

AHMAD KARIEM

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



CONTACT



Phone



Email



Website



Address

187 Cottonwood Dr. Sunset Estates, SK.



EDUCATION





University of Saskatchewan

2011 - 2015 **Bachelor of Science Honors - Biochemistry**

University of



ABOUT ME

I am a 100% self-taught full-stack developer from Saskatoon Saskatchewan. After several years of professional experience working in areas such as tech sales, marketing, and data analysis, I decided to pursue a field that has always interested me - computer programming.



EXPERIENCE



Planned Career Break

2022-2023

- Building capabilities in full-stack development
- Creating web apps using modern object-oriented programming languages and frameworks

Data Analyst **Red Wireless**

2021 - 2022

- · Managing the collection, upkeep, and analysis of company data
- Automating processes using Zapier
- Managing freelance developers and designers



SkipTheDishes

2020-2021

Territory Sales Executive

- Prospecting, pitching, and signing new restaurant partners across Saskatchewan
- · Advising new restaurant partners on best practices to succeed on Skip



Vendasta

2019 - 2020

BDR/SDR Team Lead/SDR

- As a BDR prospecting, pitching and signing new channel partners
- As SDR Team Lead Managed a team of 5 SDRs while maintaining a full SDR quota
- As an SDR Sales prospecting and connecting prospects with the BDR team



MY SKILLS & EXPERTISE

- HTML/CSS
- JavaScript
- React
- Node.js
- Express.js
- PostgreSQL
- Git

- Complex Problem Solving
- Project Management
- Communication
- Organization
- Time Management
- Presenting and **Public Speaking**



MY REFERENCES

Available upon request